let questions3 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "alley",
      answer: "C. Gasse",
      options: [
        "A. Straße",
        "B. Weg",
        "C. Gasse",
        "D. Boulevard"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "ax",
      answer: "A. Axt",
      options: [
        "A. Axt",
        "B. Säge",
        "C. Hammer",
        "D. Messer"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "bunch",
      answer: "D. Bündel",
      options: [
        "A. Stapel",
        "B. Haufen",
        "C. Menge",
        "D. Bündel"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "chore",
      answer: "B. Hausarbeit",
      options: [
        "A. Hobby",
        "B. Hausarbeit",
        "C. Vergnügen",
        "D. Spiel"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "decent",
      answer: "C. anständig",
      options: [
        "A. schlecht",
        "B. mangelhaft",
        "C. anständig",
        "D. perfekt"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "disgrace",
      answer: "A. Schande",
      options: [
        "A. Schande",
        "B. Ehre",
        "C. Stolz",
        "D. Ruhm"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "elbow",
      answer: "D. Ellbogen",
      options: [
        "A. Knie",
        "B. Schulter",
        "C. Handgelenk",
        "D. Ellbogen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "grateful",
      answer: "B. dankbar",
      options: [
        "A. undankbar",
        "B. dankbar",
        "C. gleichgültig",
        "D. verärgert"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "to irritate",
      answer: "C. reizen",
      options: [
        "A. beruhigen",
        "B. erfreuen",
        "C. reizen",
        "D. trösten"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to kid",
      answer: "A. scherzen",
      options: [
        "A. scherzen",
        "B. lügen",
        "C. drohen",
        "D. warnen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "loose",
      answer: "D. locker",
      options: [
        "A. fest",
        "B. eng",
        "C. straff",
        "D. locker"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "to offend",
      answer: "B. beleidigen",
      options: [
        "A. loben",
        "B. beleidigen",
        "C. schmeicheln",
        "D. ermutigen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "overnight",
      answer: "C. über Nacht",
      options: [
        "A. tagsüber",
        "B. morgens",
        "C. über Nacht",
        "D. abends"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "to persist",
      answer: "A. beharren",
      options: [
        "A. beharren",
        "B. aufgeben",
        "C. verzichten",
        "D. zweifeln"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "pine",
      answer: "D. Kiefer",
      options: [
        "A. Eiche",
        "B. Birke",
        "C. Buche",
        "D. Kiefer"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "scar",
      answer: "B. Narbe",
      options: [
        "A. Wunde",
        "B. Narbe",
        "C. Kratzer",
        "D. Schnitt"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "sensation",
      answer: "C. Empfindung",
      options: [
        "A. Gedanke",
        "B. Idee",
        "C. Empfindung",
        "D. Erinnerung"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "sled",
      answer: "A. Schlitten",
      options: [
        "A. Schlitten",
        "B. Fahrrad",
        "C. Roller",
        "D. Skateboard"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "to tease",
      answer: "D. hänseln",
      options: [
        "A. loben",
        "B. ermutigen",
        "C. unterstützen",
        "D. hänseln"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "valentine",
      answer: "B. Liebling",
      options: [
        "A. Freund",
        "B. Liebling",
        "C. Bekannter",
        "D. Kollege"
      ]
    }
  ];
  
  export default questions3;